{
    "b2_g4_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "498",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7120",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "6 1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "44r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "103",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "7/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "685",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "1056",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "1 1/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "119r4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "5644",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "1/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "4680",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "1 1/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "1/4 ",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "1/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "4338",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "78r5",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "40r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "1938",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "4879",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "6622",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "299",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "965",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7411",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "1 1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "54",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "137r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "61",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "(3/4,6/8)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,3],[1,2])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "6789",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "858",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "(5 1/4, 5 2/8)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "31r3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "40r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "1088",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "(1/2, 5/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "4312",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "9 3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "1/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "5238",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "71r4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "117r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "2581",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "8658",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "5241",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "627",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "9221",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4812",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "(9 1/8, 8 9/8)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,10],[3,6,9])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "32153",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,3,4,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "92",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "304r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "(3 1/2, 3 2/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,4], [1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "8667",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2241",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(1/6, 12/72)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,9],[2,4,6,8])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "40r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "10648",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": " 9 13/14",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "49802",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "8046",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "6400",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "(7,6 10/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([12],[2,4,6,8,11])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "25340",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "58",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "21r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "5 3/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "(2/5,4/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "8778",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "1350",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "13/18",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "40r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "10197",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(9, 8 9/9)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([10],[3,6,9])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "19656",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "87.7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "1.02",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "16131",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "70",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "4 1/9",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "78.4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "68.59",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "27.72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "150",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "8.35",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "32.2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "156",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12,18]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "13.65",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "3.6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "5.95",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "10.3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "74.8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "5.01",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "41888",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "110",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "3 1/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "68.58",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "8.68",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "25.83",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "210",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "9.06",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "29.4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "39",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "46.851",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "0.7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "1.75",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "10.5",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "979",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "0",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "86",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "42",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "754",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "210",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "35",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "42",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "8.35",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "941",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "420",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "705",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "67",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "867",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "56",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "0",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "82",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "75",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "174",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "26",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "80",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "815",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "720",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "45",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "430",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "388",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "29",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "86",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "71",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "93",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "81",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "46",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "57",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "67",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "52",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "95",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "78",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "37",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "23",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "44",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "23",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "67",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "93",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "38",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "38",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "86",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "71",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "96",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "33",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "91",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "49",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "31",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "80",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "17",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "75",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "59",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "70",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "51",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "87",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "97",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "41",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "65",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "77",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "34",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "86",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "87",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "93",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "92",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "35",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "73",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "78",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "50",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "17",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "69",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "94",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "85",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "34",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "61",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "53",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "37",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "89",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "31",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "41",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "93",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "68",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "66",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "691",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "0",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "84",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "38",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "403",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "92",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "83",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "902",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "540",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "188",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "37",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "27",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "423",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "64",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "663",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "77",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "872",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "54",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "68",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "78",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "35",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "931",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "82",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "900",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "180",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "171",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "64",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "810",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "237",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "0",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "70",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "610",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "71",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "150",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "286",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "81",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "501",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "78",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "97",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "279",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "54",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "74",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "36",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "305",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "71",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "740",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "100",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "136",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "36",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "84",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "387",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "847",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7020",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "2 2/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "143r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "123",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "7/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "6886",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "209",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "(8 1/4, 8 3/12)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,5],[1,2,3,4])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "80r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "7128",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "3156",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "(7 2/5,7 4/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,5], [1,2,3,4])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "2/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "7/12",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "5803",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "156r3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "132r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "1495",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "1746",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "9206",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "408",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "398",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7132",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "9 3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "56",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "96r3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "262",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "3/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "4359",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "198",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "(5 3/4, 5 6/8)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "31r4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "2688",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "3/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "7974",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "2 1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "2/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "5/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "3934",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "72r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "206r3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "2755",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "4089",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "5006",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "861",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "898",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7121",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "1 1/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "54",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "98r6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "67",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "7/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "3887",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "492",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "1 1/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "101r8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "1184",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "5124",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "(7 1/2, 7 2/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "2/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "(1/2, 3/6)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,3],[1,2])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "5634",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "258r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "200r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "2024",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "6877",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "3421",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_a_25": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "627",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "898",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "3632",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "6 2/3",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "184r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "340",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "(1/2,3/6)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,3],[1,2])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "6488",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "869",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "11 7/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "313r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "4704",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "(1/2,2/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,3],[1,2])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "1518",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "(7 1/2,7 2/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "1/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "5/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "4904",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "46r8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "111r2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "650",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "6287",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "9101",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_b_25": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "25",
        "Answer": "935",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "8005",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "2730",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "3 1/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "61625",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "76",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "90r6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "4 1/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "6529",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2244",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "39/40",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "50",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "9823",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(10 7/18, 9 25/18)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,0,12],[2,4,6,8,11])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "43378",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "6242",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7414",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "4 1/14",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "52272",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "84",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "445r1",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "6 4/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "(1/5, 2/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,4],[1,2,3])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "7776",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "5352",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "25/36",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "50",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "5830",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(5 9/10, 5 18/20, 59/10, 118/20)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,14], [0,0,0,0,13], [0,0,0,13], [2,4,6,9,12])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "16020",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "9512",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "7975",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "(3 7/10, 37/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,15],[3,6,10,14])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "33733",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "102r4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "(9 1/2, 9 5/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,5],[1,2,3,4])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "(1/2, 2/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,3],[1,2])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "1849",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "4144",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(1 22/63, 85/63)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,0,9],[2,4,6,8])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "10263",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "9 7/12",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "12972",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "8733",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4860",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "(10 1/4, 9 5/4, 10 2/8, 9 10/8)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,12], [0,0,11], [0,0,0,11], [2,4,7,10])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "28210",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "38",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "50r4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "9 3/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "4/5",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "4806",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "6244",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(1 23/35, 58/35, 1 46/70, 116/70)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,0,0,11], [0,0,0,10], [0,0,0,0,10], [1,3,5,7,9])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "280",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "4660",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(5, 4 4/4)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([10],[3,6,9])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "72384",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "88.9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "1.32",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "45708",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "190",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "(3 1/6, 3 3/18)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,9],[2,4,6,8])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "40.72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "46.81",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "96.72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "610",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "9.02",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "8.1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "199",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12,18]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "70.848",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "0.3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "1.79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "10.3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "68.3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "1.11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "61542",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "5 1/9",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "63.21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "26.79",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "88.83",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "50",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "7.05",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "9.8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "225",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10,16]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "23.736",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "1.8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "4.85",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "10.7",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "49.8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "2.22",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "20925",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "(9 4/5, 9 8/10)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,9],[2,4,6,8])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "63.15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "53.48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "38.88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "310",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "8.63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "15.6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "96",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "50.735",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "0.6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "2.34",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "10.3",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "86.9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "3.12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "61304",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5,8,11,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "110",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "(3 1/2, 3 6/12)",
        "Scoring Method": "4",
        "Scores": "([0,0,9],[2,4,6,8])",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "30.5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "72.57",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "48.99",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "320",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "6.1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "28.8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "114",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10,16]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "13.794",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,9,12,15]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "1.2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "5.48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "40.2",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[4,7,10,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "13",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "17",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g1_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "13",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g1_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_a_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "a",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "13",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_21": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "21",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_22": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "22",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_23": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "23",
        "Answer": "19",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g1_b_24": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "1",
        "Form": "b",
        "Problem": "24",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": "CAP BEGINS ON THIS LINE"
    },
    "b1_g2_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_1d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1d",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_1e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1e",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_8": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "613",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_13f": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13f",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g2_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "71",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_d_8": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "497",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_13f": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13f",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g2_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "37",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_1d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1d",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "22",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_d_8": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "339",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,5,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "23",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_13f": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13f",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "50",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g2_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "2",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "46",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "250",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "300",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "740",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3d",
        "Answer": "700",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3e",
        "Answer": "220",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3f": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3f",
        "Answer": "200",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3g": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3g",
        "Answer": "840",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_3h": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3h",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "5/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "8/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_16a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16a",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_16b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16b",
        "Answer": "00",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "64",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "84",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "44",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g3_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "112",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "11",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "06",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "3/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "370",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "400",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "940",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3d",
        "Answer": "900",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3e",
        "Answer": "760",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3f": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3f",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3g": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3g",
        "Answer": "830",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_3h": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3h",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "48",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "4/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "8/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "56",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "52",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_16a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16a",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_16b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16b",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "36",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g3_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "117",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "57",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "2/8",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "500",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "500",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "260",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3d",
        "Answer": "300",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3e",
        "Answer": "770",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3f": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3f",
        "Answer": "800",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3g": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3g",
        "Answer": "630",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_3h": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3h",
        "Answer": "600",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "6/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "3/1",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "68",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "84",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_16a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16a",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_16b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16b",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "76",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "63",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g3_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "3",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "128",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "(no,n)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_2c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "X%4=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "X%4=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "X%4=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "22",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_5c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "135",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "c",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "(a,d)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_7c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7c",
        "Answer": "(b,e,f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "2500",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "2460",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "2000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "4700",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "4670",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "5000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "=",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "120",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "420",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "240",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "60000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "8000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "400",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "70",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_d_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "215",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10,16]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_15a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15a",
        "Answer": "(0.9, .9)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_15b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15b",
        "Answer": "(0.79, .79)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "2.88",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_17a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17a",
        "Answer": "(37,83)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_17b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17b",
        "Answer": "(37,83)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_17c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17c",
        "Answer": "(90,88)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_17d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17d",
        "Answer": "(90,88)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "2 1/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g4_e_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "9",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "(no,n)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "(no,n)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_2c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2c",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "X%3=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "X%3=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "X%3=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "33",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_5c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "192",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9,14]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "e",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "(a,b,d)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_7c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7c",
        "Answer": "(c,f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "8300",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "8260",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "8000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "6400",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "6440",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "6000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "48",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "64",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "80",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "40000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "3000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "700",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "90",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_d_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "198",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10,16]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_15a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15a",
        "Answer": "(.1,0.1)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_15b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15b",
        "Answer": "(.35,0.35)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "2.16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,6,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_17a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17a",
        "Answer": "(41,67)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_17b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17b",
        "Answer": "(41,67)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_17c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17c",
        "Answer": "(24,25)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_17d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17d",
        "Answer": "(24,25)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "2 1/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g4_e_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "(no,n)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "(no,n)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_2c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2c",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "X%8=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "X%8=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "X%8=0",
        "Scoring Method": "9",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "23",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_5c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5c",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "123",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8,13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "f",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "(a,b)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_7c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7c",
        "Answer": "(c,d,e)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "8200",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "8180",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "8000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "7300",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "7290",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "7000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "8000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "3000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "6000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "20000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "9000",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "500",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_13d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13d",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_d_13e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "13e",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "178",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10,16]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_15a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15a",
        "Answer": "(.6,0.6)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_15b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15b",
        "Answer": "(.61,0.61)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "7.85",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,6,8,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_17a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17a",
        "Answer": "(37,47)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_17b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17b",
        "Answer": "(37,47)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_17c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17c",
        "Answer": "(48,60)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_17d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "17d",
        "Answer": "(48,60)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "3 1/4",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[3,6,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g4_e_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "4",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_3": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "19/24",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6a",
        "Answer": "7.5",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6b",
        "Answer": "7.48",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6c",
        "Answer": "7.478",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6d",
        "Answer": "6.4",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6e",
        "Answer": "6.44",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_c_6f": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6f",
        "Answer": "6.436",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "25",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "35",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8g": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8g",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8h": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8h",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_8i": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8i",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "80",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "1/24",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,3,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_11": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "1.92",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9,14,19]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "3.6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g5_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "1/16",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_3": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "29",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "5/6",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6a",
        "Answer": "3.2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6b",
        "Answer": "3.18",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6c",
        "Answer": "3.183",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6d",
        "Answer": "9.2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6e",
        "Answer": "9.16",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_c_6f": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6f",
        "Answer": "9.162",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "10",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "12",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "14",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8g": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8g",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8h": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8h",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_8i": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8i",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "2/15",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,3,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_11": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "3.28",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10,15,20]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "80",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "2.8",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g5_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "3/32",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_1a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1a",
        "Answer": "<",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_1b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1b",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_1c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1c",
        "Answer": ">",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_2": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_3": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6,12]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[13]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_5": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5",
        "Answer": "13/15",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6a",
        "Answer": "4.2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6b",
        "Answer": "4.22",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6c",
        "Answer": "4.222",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6d",
        "Answer": "4.4",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6e",
        "Answer": "4.38",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_c_6f": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6f",
        "Answer": "4.379",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_7a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7a",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_7b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7b",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8c",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8d",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8e",
        "Answer": "21",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8f": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8f",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8g": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8g",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8h": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8h",
        "Answer": "32",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_8i": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8i",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_9": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_d_10": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10",
        "Answer": "1/24",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[1,3,5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_11": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11",
        "Answer": "3.60",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[5,10,15,20]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_13": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13",
        "Answer": "126",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_14": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14",
        "Answer": "5.6",
        "Scoring Method": "3",
        "Scores": "[1,3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g5_e_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "5",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "1/28",
        "Scoring Method": "2",
        "Scores": "[2,4,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_1": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "24:61",
        "Scoring Method": "5",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "5",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "576",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7,14,21]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "(true,t)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "(false, f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_9a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_9b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9b",
        "Answer": "30",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_9c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9c",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_9d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9d",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "-8",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_d_10c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10c",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "($10,10)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "($15,15)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "($25,25)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_11d": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11d",
        "Answer": "(yes, y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_11e": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11e",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "75",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "46",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "88",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "(diver b, b)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "28",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "64",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_f_16": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "150",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,7,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_f_17": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "56",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[5,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_f_18": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b1_g6_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "1",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_1": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "17:24",
        "Scoring Method": "5",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "140",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,6,10]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "1120",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7,13,19,26]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "(false, f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "(false, f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_9a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_9b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9b",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_9c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9c",
        "Answer": "36",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_9d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9d",
        "Answer": "15",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "-5",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_d_10c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10c",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "($50,50)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "($75,75)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "($125,125)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_11d": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11d",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_11e": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11e",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "97",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "55",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "(diver b,b)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "27",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[3,7]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_f_16": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "160",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7,15,23]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_f_17": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "72",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_f_18": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b2_g6_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "2",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_1": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "1",
        "Answer": "16:18",
        "Scoring Method": "5",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_2a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2a",
        "Answer": "6",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[11]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_2b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "2b",
        "Answer": "7",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_3a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3a",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_3b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3b",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_3c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "3c",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_4": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "4",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[3,6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_5a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5a",
        "Answer": "60",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_5b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "5b",
        "Answer": "480",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[7,14,21]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_c_6": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "c",
        "Problem": "6",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[6]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_7": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "7",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_8a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8a",
        "Answer": "(false,f)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_8b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "8b",
        "Answer": "(true,t)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_9a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9a",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_9b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9b",
        "Answer": "18",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_9c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9c",
        "Answer": "36",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_9d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "9d",
        "Answer": "20",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_10a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10a",
        "Answer": "-3",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_10b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10b",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_d_10c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "d",
        "Problem": "10c",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_11a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11a",
        "Answer": "($80,80)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_11b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11b",
        "Answer": "($120,120)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_11c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11c",
        "Answer": "($200,200)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_11d": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11d",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_11e": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "11e",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Scoring Method": "8",
        "Scores": "[1,2,3]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_12": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "12",
        "Answer": "8",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_13a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13a",
        "Answer": "94",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_13b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13b",
        "Answer": "66",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_13c": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "13c",
        "Answer": "98",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[2]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_14a": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14a",
        "Answer": "(diver a,a)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_14b": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "14b",
        "Answer": "24",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[1]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_e_15": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "e",
        "Problem": "15",
        "Answer": "16",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[2,4]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_f_16": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "16",
        "Answer": "40",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[10,20]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_f_17": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "17",
        "Answer": "54",
        "Scoring Method": "1",
        "Scores": "[4,8]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_f_18": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "18",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Scoring Method": "6",
        "Scores": "[9]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_f_19": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "19",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[5]",
        "": ""
    },
    "b3_g6_f_20": {
        "Benchmark": "3",
        "Grade": "6",
        "Form": "f",
        "Problem": "20",
        "Answer": "(yes,y)",
        "Scoring Method": "7",
        "Scores": "[4]",
        "": ""
    }
}